Music
Thank you for watching
Good morning.
Yes, what's your name?
My name is Kosaku Koizumi. I have my own geiko.
The origin of my name is so that I can be a person who can make your light bloom.
I am Kosaku, the light blooms.
What do people call you?
The members call me Ko-chan, Kosaku, and Gawayuru.
Where are you from?
I am from Miyagi, Japan.
My birthday is March 11.
What is your blood type?
Type A.
What is your favorite part of your face?
My eyelashes.
Eyelashes
My hobby is visiting ramen shops.
I am good at soccer.
Do something interesting.
My eyelashes
My favorite food is ramen
What's your least favorite food?
Raw carrots.
My favorite colors are white and blue.
My strength is that I can do a lot of things without thinking.
My weakness is that I am a pain in the ass.
I have a habit of saying...
I wonder what it is...
My eyelashes are gone.
I have a big mole here.
What is it about your personality that you want to fix?
I'm a pain in the ass.
What made you laugh recently?
Uh...
I don't know.
What made you laugh recently?
I went to Jiro Ramen with Takato.
I went with Takato.
I was so nervous about the call
I was so nervous about the call that I chewed a little.
It was a funny episode.
Lately
I've been having trouble getting out of bed.
I always do.
I always fall asleep twice.
I always wake up about 10 minutes before I leave the house.
Daily routine
Take a shower in the morning
I wake up even though it's 10 minutes before I leave
If you could take one thing with you to a deserted island, what would it be?
A boat.
I'm in.
Psychic powers.
Uh, I'd like to go back in time and start over.
If you won the lottery, what would you do with it?
Buy a house?
Buy a car.
Get a driver's license.
A car.
Yes.
Stress reliever?
Sleeping.
What is your treasure?
A picture of a live concert
Earliest memory
The story of how you didn't speak at all until you were 3 years old.
That's all I said.
Playing air guitar.
Air guitar.
Who is the kindest person in your life?
Jun.
The hardest?
Chazz and me, I guess.
Surprising aspects of the members
Since Kaname became the leader, he has become very aggressive.
Who has the most poker face in real life?
Poker face? I guess I am.
It doesn't show on my face.
What do you think you are in real life?
In reality? I am to reality.
I wonder.
One-seventh.
I don't know the members.
I eat tsukemen more than ramen these days.
What is the one thing you can't lose to anyone?
Hmmm...
I'm pretty decisive.
Who would you like to meet?
My future self
I'm on a muscle training kick these days.
See you in the next video!
If I'm only off for a day, I'll just relax at my place.
But if I'm free every day, I'll go out to various places.
Like Broggy.
What was he like?
I didn't talk much.
Favorite comedian?
I don't know.
I don't really watch them.
Kamaitachi.
Sandwich Man.
I love them because they're from my hometown.
I love them.
Well...
I want to sleep and be done with it.
If I could be reborn.
I'd like to be myself again.
Myself.
Light.
All right.
I say good
Trip
Oh, but Kazuto and I and Kaname...
We were talking about going to Kyoto.
Do you forget bad things easily?
It drags on for a day or two.
And then...
I completely forget about it.
What's your fetish?
Hmmm...
Hmm. I don't know.
Let's see...
Flip-flops?
I don't know.
I don't know if you know.
Today.
Here's a question from the observers.
Oh, hey.
What's your favorite outfit?
I've always said it's the Shine Spear costume.
You keep saying that.
What's your favorite onigiri ingredient?
My favorite onigiri...
Lately I've been eating a lot of tuna mayo.
What's important to you?
Well...
To be true to my own opinion.
What is your favorite phrase from your part?
Well, the one that comes to mind
I can only come up with with approval.
It's all about you.
Give me your blessing.
What was your favorite sport?
Uh...
Balls.
It's easy.
If you could reward yourself for something, what would it be?
No, I don't think I'd like that.
What is your favorite choreographed local language song?
Let's see...
"Sinking to Infinite Death" took a lot of work to choreograph.
I was so happy when I finished it.
I still think it's a song that holds a lot of memories for me.
What do you want to eat now?
Ramen noodles!
If you had 7 days off, what would you do?
Well, if I had 7 days off, I would like to go on a trip.
I would like to go on a trip with the members.
If you were a family of 7, what would your family consist of?
Let's see...
Jun-kun is my grandfather
Taka is a mother
Ryota is
Ji...
Masaya is
E-san
And Karami is the father
And Kazuto is
Kazuto is Yon
and I'm the grandmother
So it's like that?
Yes, sir.
Where do you like to sit in the upper room?
Uh, middle of the room, by the window.
It's the least conspicuous.
Compose a composition about me in the local section
Compose ayu in the local section
We're the cause of the problem
Hmmm
Don't you think
view of the world
We lose track of time
With a momentum that blows you away.
Not quite right, is it?
It's hard to say.
What if I were to compare the members to oden?
What? If you compare the members to oden ingredients?
What?
Jun-kun is...
I wonder what Jun-kun is.
Jun-kun would be a chikuwa (sticky rice cakes).
And Takato?
Takato is, um, mochi kinchaku.
Haname is...
Karame is konnyaku.
Ryota is radish
Kazuto is string konnyaku
Because it's late
Masaya makes cabbage rolls
I'm Hanpen.
If you could change the color of your e-mail, what color would it be?
Blue. I've always liked blue since I was little.
I loved it.
Like the stock that grandpa can't take.
Like the kind of stock your grandfather couldn't take.
Big stock.
Big stock! Big stock!
What do you find attractive about real language?
I think it's the world view that no other group can offer.
Is it a fun song to sing?
You can have the crude oil.
I can hear everyone's voices, so it's a lot of fun.
Favorite emoji?
Favorite pictogram?
This one. That's right.
There's a picture that's not very emotional.
Can you tell?
Today's breakfast is a rice ball with tuna mayo, boiled egg, and miso soup.
I've been eating a lot lately. I've been eating a lot for breakfast.
I've been getting up early a lot lately, so I've been eating a lot.
Time to rest?
Falling asleep after taking a bath is the best.
Rehearsal Ramune... I always have Ramune.
I really don't know what I've been doing.
In junior high school, my dream was to be a nursery school teacher.
And your mother's dream?
Junkun. I'd like to keep going even if someone ignores me.
Even if someone ignores you, you keep talking about it, and I want to follow your strong will.
What if you were an animal?
I'm often lazy.
If you could switch places for a day, what would you be?
I would like to be Kaname, because I think Kaname is the most active person in the local section.
I think Kaname is the most independent person in the department.
I've been to Korea by myself.
Where would you like to perform in a country other than Japan?
But Kaname and I were talking about how we wanted to go to Korea.
So I would like to go to Korea, eat samgyeopsal and perform there.
Who do you respect?
Well, how about Supertokkyu?
Every time I see them dance or perform, I think they are amazing.
Movies you want to see?
Oh, but Marvels has been playing recently.
Marvels has been recommended by all my friends and the members.
I'd like to go see it.
Clothes?
I'm looking for clothes that fit me and not everyone else.
I'm trying to find something that fits me.
At a bakery.
Melon bread and cod roe bread.
Sweet and salty.
What appeals to you?
I have no doubts.
Three things that happened this week
Three good things?
Early to bed
Waking up early and eating breakfast
Good.
What's the source of your energy?
Well, I guess...
I guess that's what it's all about.
What's your favorite side dish?
My favorite side dish is eggplant.
What's next for you? What's your next song?
Well, I don't know... I think "Slight Dream of a Dream".
It's got a lot of song splits, and it starts in the center and ends in the center, so I think it stands out the most.
I think it will stand out the most.
I think I was a dandelion in a previous life.
The dandelion. What's a dandelion?
Oh, it's yellow. It's different. What is it? Not a dandelion.
Dandelion fluff.
I was a dandelion boll in a previous life.
My last supper...
Ramen noodles.
I like to sit by the window on the bullet train.
I'm always in the middle of the train when I'm there.
Everyone likes the window, so we tend to be in the middle of the three seats.
The place I want to go to most now is Kyoto.
I want to go to Kyoto to enjoy hot springs and eat sweets.
What foreign Chinese words have you learned recently?
I learned it from the song "Welcome Back" and "Museum Zero".
What is your motto?
My motto: "Two birds with one stone.
Am I right?
Show us your favorite recent photo.
Yes, here it is.
This is...
I recently ate at a ramen restaurant.
Am I right?
It's a ramen shop called "Golden Otogisu".
You can change the flavor a couple of times.
It was delicious!
When do you feel happy in winter?
When I'm under the covers.
What are the 420 things that come to mind?
Two birds with one stone.
That's all I can think of.
What sport are you good at?
I'm good at soccer.
What impressed you the most?
I dreamt that I was being chased.
I was being chased.
I got scared and ran away.
And before I knew it, we became friends.
And we were running together.
I don't know what it was about.
When I was a child, I dreamed of being a policeman.
I said I wanted to be a policeman.
When you were in McE...
Coffee? Tea?
Uh, tea, basically.
What's your favorite doughnut?
Soft doughnuts.
What do you mean?
How do you say your favorite doughnut is...
The soft kind.
Like the ones with chocolate in them.
Uh...
Choco.
No, matcha.
Matcha doughnuts.
You said they're soft.
I like those cookie-like donuts.
It's called a matcha old fashioned.
Yes.
My specialty is mille-feuille casserole.
It's the easiest.
You just put it in.
And then just pop it in.
I can just pop it in.
What would you like to challenge yourself with?
I want to get better at lifting.
What local song would you like people to listen to most?
Uh...
I don't know.
I guess Museum Zero.
It's also the newest song.
What would you like to do this year...
Well...
I don't know.
Ah!
Go to one more precious-style ramen restaurant
By the end of this year
One last thing.
Yes, sir!
I got 100 questions!
Yay!
Thank you for watching!